The voice is collide, the storm and the flame, laughter and chaos, it's part of the game, secrets unravel, the stage is alive, in Psyche's arena, the strange will survive.
Who's afraid?
Let it break from shadows to starlight
The truth will be shown
The psyche awakens you're never alone
Expect the unexpected
Strange and unusual
Step inside the flow
The circus of shadows
It's Psyche's show
Terrible trolls in the dark
Take their stand
But angels are dancing
Torchlight in head
It's Psyche's show
She whispers in flames
Please hide and seek with the shadow
My beautiful beach, please.
How my life has changed.
Do I have any other options for my traveling?
See beautiful beach.
How about?
We're in the after, but at documents.
Oh excuse me. Document desktop. I hear that. Broadcast. Uh-oh.
Bound name all.
Pew.
Okay.
How are you guys doing? Ghost said please open the panel as we go.
I'll do one more time for ghosty.
Just one more, though. Just one more.
I had like a bunch of these really cool images.
Not here they are, I think.
See if it works.
Oh, there it goes.
Because those have to say in the studio. How are you guys doing there? I'm
Very nice there. Oh my
Logo, where's everybody? I don't know what you talk. Is my chat working?
I think I'll play one more. Hey with some Gotti. What's up? What's up? What's up?
Goes wanting to start one more channel because I don't know he's like, oh, I want it
Want to crash out you go ahead? Oh
Okay, I
Want to put here's the song I made for Alexandria yesterday, and I want to play it again. It's really good
It's called neon neon priestess
Alexandra's got the mic, telling truth with a grin.
IRL News, where the real begins.
She's gorgeous, she's weak.
Got fa-
Yes
Thank you, buddy. Good to see you, sir. Nice to meet you
Who is that other guy? Nice to meet you, sir
I've actually got him. This is the real guy, but I don't know about him
Do you ever remember the band called The Misfits, psyche? We are...
What are those 3D glasses?
We are 138.
Idiot.
What is this one?
What fucking blow you do tonight?
Man of reference or something?
His voice changed.
Sharon, his voice just changed.
God, are you okay?
Yeah, you're almost there. I'm not in the house.
I'm almost there right now.
You sound like you got something in your mouth, man.
No, I'm just a son, I'm not in the house.
Thank you for letting me know, baby.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm about to kick God off because he's annoying.
Oh, really?
Fuck you, then, you bitch-ass motherfucker.
Where's my baby Bita?
Where's my little baby Bita?
That's why I love baby. I'll turn my camera on. I need baby be the be the get up here, sweetie
You might have a turn my camera off like I don't be
Listen you guys always gonna fight but you and be you're like brothers and sisters man you guys like brothers and sisters
stop
but even if she's a sister she don't have to treat you the way she treats you so she's the evil sister actually
yeah she's an evil sister
it's like Cinderella like the evil stepmother right
oh this and that I love you this and that you know Abida this and that
No, that's what she, I love when Bita says this and that.
I actually, it's the other day, I was at work and somebody was talking to me and I was like,
that's it, that, I'm like, why did you say that to me?
Like, what is this and that?
And I was like, oh, that's a Bita thing.
And they're like, what?
And I was like, oh, it's a YouTube thing.
And I was like, shut the fuck up, idiot.
And I was like, all right, I sound like an idiot now.
Not now, like right here, but at work, I sound like an idiot.
Because I was like, this and that, this and that.
And you're like Joe, why are you keep saying this and that this and that and I was like I love my baby Deedah
I love my baby Deedah. I said like Joe Joe
Well, you interrupted me when I was talking we go ahead
This and that
If I ever, I'm a single man, if I ever was in real life
and I met a woman like Bita, I'm like, you know what?
That's the women I can fall in love with.
That's a woman I can actually meet.
She's nice, she takes care of her cats.
She's very nice to her pets.
So right there, when you know, right there from me,
if somebody takes care of their pets,
that's already like a fucking,
Thumbs up in my book and also beat is sexy. So that's that's two good things
She takes care of her pets and she's good-looking
Oh
I'm sorry. It's like I thought I was talking. I apologize
Oh, I see the screen it looks like golem. Is that oh whose face is he holding? Is that crystal Marie's face?
I do love Chris and Marie, but there's a difference the way I love Bita
Cuz be the could be somebody that I actually could actually care about beat is a good come on guys
Let's all be honest beat is anybody and anybody that's in the chat
Like beat is this beat is that and each note? Let me say one thing's like any faggot fucking trolls
I didn't mean to say the effort I maggot maggot maggot any maggots that come into be this channel
They're only saying that cuz they love her
Everybody knows who the fuck do you love? I love me
My baby
They sent back
We looking at boy
And I gotta give you credit those glasses are fucking badass. I gotta give you credit. There's pretty bad in places. Thank you
I love you Vita
What was I gonna show you? Oh, yeah, here look at much this
Is it gonna be me kissing you because if it is I'm fucking gonna call the cops it's gonna be
We're having sex in this video
I mean, if you want me to kiss you in real life. Just give me fucking 50 bucks. Christ. I'll give you a little kiss, man
Just give me a hundred dollars like a hundred thousand dollars
Actually, you know what you couldn't pay me enough to kiss you but beta
I could get me to for free
And I'm watching
Oh, there she is my girl crystal. What the hell is this is that?
There she is there's my girl
God damn Chris Lee sweet little dude
That Sam is!
Hallelujah!
I could just like love your whole life, you know?
Yeah.
You're so not nice though.
I know that's not really crisp though, but that's a good memory.
I remember you, Crystal. I love you when you say things like that.
I
I'm predictable I don't think you do I don't really think you know who I am actually
I love you all. You don't even know who I am, actually.
I know. I know.
That's not a funny thing.
That's not a little better.
That is what it is.
A tagging crystal.
I know it's not live, but I love a crystal filled pack.
You are not a good...
You're not a good guy, sluggy, crystal feather.
You're not a good guy.
You are not very nice to a lot of people.
You know what, because you don't even know who I am, so therefore you are getting me next
up for somebody else to go fucking die bitch.
Well, you don't even know who I am you're fucking
Everything on life you have no fucking control on everything in life
And you've died on everything on life, and you have no control and everything in life, and you have no life
Wow that was the Lord's help telling you
I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling
So yeah, I mean this from the bottom of my heart hold. I only have one heart
I mean this from a one-heart
Crystal really is so fucking cool because she gets shrunk and she don't care what she says
She's not here to kiss like anybody's ass
Crystal just says what's in her mind and I'll always love her for that because she don't give a fuck
Do you see what she said?
Person
There she is. Oh
Sorry, I mean, she's Louise who does some God
Therapy within 10 minutes crystal really
You don't know shit, dude.
Yeah, yeah, they're being too...
Nah, I like not talking about before he's stupid bitch,
or he's stupid or he's doggy.
Oh, Crystal Marie!
See, that's what I love about Crystal.
Like, you're the one who's stupid.
He just wants to just slap her fucking guy.
Thank you, Crystal.
And I know you're not live.
I know it's not live,
but I still talk to you like it is.
Oh, shut up, Christine.
Oh, Christine, why don't we just use that match each other before we talk to us?
Sure, Christine.
Two blonde hairs that, uh, like, bleach.
How the fuck can you not love christenry? I don't care if you're a fucking gay guy like your days like no offense
You're gay. How can you not love christenry?
Christine go to bed go to bed
I just woke up one a couple hours ago and I was like oh my gosh Christina
Christina you need to go to bed I just woke up one a couple hours ago and it's been a bleed
I just woke up well you know what go to bed bitch
I'm about to bleed
I'm about to bleed I don't know Chris so much
Oh my gosh this bitch is trying to say I'm making a fool out of myself
She's well said, well said sweetheart
I know you're not live Chris, but when I'm still talking to the live chat
I'm just still talking to Chris, but even though I know Chris is not live
Bullying all of us Christine has been bullying like every female and every male like
He was like bullying people that didn't even need it birds. I got birds all over this like
And that bird is chirping.
What?
Is the popo still watching us today?
Oh
No, yeah, every time I come in here you say the popo's watching us
Dude I never said the popo's were watching you
Watching you every time
you crack or no crystals right that whore was
trippin that whore was trippin summer baby
i love summer oh hell yes summer i fuck with bro christy
what the fuck i'm crack or christy is a crack or
you're fucking talking about my girl fucking summer like she can
fucking like if she even has a fucking right to
I
See
She's still I know it's not even live and I'm someone to go ahead
Irvi you only have to fight over summer, right?
Is this live or is this a clip?
I don't know what I'm talking about.
He apparently doesn't know. You know that, right?
You know why I would never...
Because I would never get my animal like you did?
Yeah, I feel like she abused her dog.
Oh, Chris said beautiful.
You see my dog.
You see how beautiful my dog is.
She's a beautiful dog.
Chris, you're funny.
You're so fucking crazy. Oh, yeah, he's really abused. Yeah
I don't mean ever told this but but out of everybody ever met Kristen Reed to the audience
So I
Know
are you losing your mind she is she's not losing her mind
christen's right he's living a five-star resort right yeah only our dogs in a
five-star resort wow think that dog is the happiest
the
Oh, no.
Myself.
Well, she was trying to make everybody else be at me now, so now come, she can prove herself.
Well, that's a good question. I wish I would have been on this live
She said I'll never have your love I'm thinking why
You understand that it fucking doesn't matter
I love the way that you are but see these other people I cannot do it because they're so fucking retarded they
They're not themselves. They fake themselves. Okay. Okay. They fake
Okay, this bitch
She's pretty, she's pretty honest, she is.
Well, you know what, Christine, yeah, she's a liar bitch, and this is what I'm talking about.
I'm actually, I know her whole life, like, offline, we know each other and I know her as well as I do.
You're a liar bitch, you're a liar bitch.
Okay, here we go. I guess you know her like you know Marcy, right?
Well these bitches do weird shit on the internet. It's fucking weird dude. I don't know what the fuck is going on.
I can tell you but I know every move Christine's made on the internet in the last four years.
You know her 12 accounts that she's acting as?
Well, it's okay. Oh, she has to have a cat. Well, you need to put me on game. Is my friend a secret?
Oh, you a bitch you want you want to bust out for an
She's got all my stuff. I want to know
I don't like that fucking backhanded compliment shit. I don't like people that do that stuff. That backhanded fucking compliment bullshit.
Yeah, that was a backhanded compliment.
I say exactly how I feel and I don't want to talk to you again.
Thank you, Chris. No, it's very rare where people actually say how they feel. I know I'm not talking to you. I'm talking to a clip
But not all people are real up here. Chris. It was fucking real man. She's fucking real
You're being a bad friend to our girl
Wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
I don't like people that go out for people to her people and like are like dirty a
discussion more you eat it like you what was that you're eating
The birds
Can we see your face you have to take a shit everybody knows that we see it on your face. I just did like
well said Chris you all well said baby just talk to God I got off the phone with him
he said
Well, I love gymnast
is a weirdo, she's right, that guy is a fucking weirdo.
Why didn't you fuck this up?
He's shitting his fucking ass.
Yeah.
That's your bitch.
That is a rock.
Thank you.
dude, you're right as big as a boulder
everybody can see it from behind
is it too big?
is it too big for my car?
is that a hair or a fucking piece of a grand canyon?
cause that's the same thing
crystal always wins
crystal was funny and shit
And the morning lights play manic monday by um that fucking
Hey mason yeah what's up dude how are you i'll do it okay hey so you actually know powder
I was actually on his channel a thing before like on his stream. You are before
Yeah
A while ago. Yeah, you ever heard of the guy named sasquash or something like that
Yeah, I think so
Sasquash was a guy that was like the owner. I think of one of the channels that he a powder dusty was on
Yeah, yeah, he promotes on my my discord sometimes
But I miss you. I mean I miss you. Where are you where we've been?
I've been just I've been doing this stuff like you know like getting things done like going to the store and get it
Stuff at the store and just getting things done
Which store do you go to the hustler hustler store?
No, you know for shit food and stuff like that, you know stuff for the whole stuff for the whole
Okay
Yeah, I mean all I have is like I just have a room full of dildos and that's all I don't buy
It's like well, why don't you why don't you like to buy food anymore? I do I'm just kidding
I do but it's like I like to go pick up food like out and like you know it deliver this
You're rather like no you rather food that you can get from like a restaurant instead of like grocery store stuff
Yeah, or like or like I have like you know a boyfriend that will make me do the kormi meals. That's awesome. Are you good cook?
I don't really know how to cook that good. I mean, that's why it's order stuff sometimes. Well, I think that too
Yeah, well, you know how to order we're gonna be good
We're just kidding. You're you're you're cool guy. I want to check I want to protect you because
You seem like sweet and innocent. Yeah
You really know the guy names, uh, I think his name is like sasquatch or something like that or something like that
Yeah, I know sasquatch. What's up with him? What's wrong with him?
Are you talking about sasquatch? What's wrong? What's going on, buddy? What's wrong with sasquatch?
I was I was in this channel with somebody named powder Dusty and he's he was on this channel
I think like right a site like you're watching a mic on this channel
What did you do what did he do?
You know, I didn't do anything wrong
It's just I just brought him up because I saw that same guy on
Sasquatch's channel that was on this channel
Never had sex with sauce well, I wouldn't let you know I seen a sasquatch and he was fucking jerking off
And I was like God you weirdo like I'm not trying to be up here to watch you jerk off you fag it or bag it like come on
And he's like all right, I'm jerking off. I'll stop jerking off now
Leave the sasquatches alone and like if you didn't want to see it you just have to like, you know
Turn off your webcam. Yeah, I didn't want to say I want to dream about it
But who said that I I've never seen him do that kind of stuff. So, okay. No, I've never seen him do it either
My mind Joe took off that he has like red pubic hair and was
Actually, I actually stay my body completely of no hair. So I've actually I have no hair on my body
It's like and actually you look you remind me of a hairy animal
Yeah, run your hair to your greasy hair. Yeah, look at your hands to your greasy hair boy
So I guess that a friend of yours or who is that guy?
What's his name is his name Joe or something like that? Yeah, it's Joe Schmo
Yeah, I never I never seen that guy before where's he from or where did he come from I think he comes from
From Texas and he's a big Dallas Cowboys fan
No, I'm seeing how did he get on your stream though?
Must have been like looking away for a second and somebody let him on because I have no idea
Did you even want him on your did you even want him on your stream though? Are you channel? I don't I don't
Go and he says the n-word to sometimes I have to like you know in my stream
But he was he was going too far with sasquatch Friday
He's talking about him doing this stuff like that. Was it appropriate to do that kind of thing like I don't know
But uh, are you know crow this guy crow? He's a Scottish
is a
a
Oh, it's kind of boring if I was named sasquatch. I would like you know cover myself in body hair and
Yeah, but Sonic it's weird because you had the same guy that was on his panel before the guy named the powder
Outer dusty. I know we're like there's all these coincidences like I think everyone knows each other and then it's like and they're all like
Preheading that they don't and they're all like messing with my head. What do you think about that?
I don't know like why would you think that?
Because they're gone insane since I met everybody
You know gaslighting the gaslighting this gaslighting. Oh, I don't know the definition of gaslighting
gaslighting is like
Messing with your head and then like making you think that you're going crazy, but you're messing with your head, right?
May I say one thing to your friends like may I say one thing to your friend?
Moon the dreamer
He said dreamer. You're a good guy, but I've actually heard this likes a big fuck
I lost him. I didn't see that part. I'm so sorry. Sorry. Did you decide did you drop him down or did he just leave?
I think it was like a bad connection because he just like a plastic and it just cut out. Oh my gosh. I'm so sorry Joe
So sorry
But I want to talk to Mace. I don't want Joe here anymore. I'm trying to talk to Mason
I think Joe's always trying to cock block, but
He doesn't need to do that, right?
It's up to you though psych is this is your channel. Yeah, I don't want him to cock block me anymore
I want to have a block cock full access to Mason
So we're still cool cycle. Oh, of course. We never were not cool. They're always cool
What is that ladies name that you said I first found you on her stream and you're playing the thing that look like a
Drone or something like that a metal thing with those metal
There is there is kiddies
How do you spell that though?
It's spelled B E E T a as kiddies
Can he's can he's can he's show me or type it to me or something I can show you hold on show you her
Yeah
Yeah, this is Sarah
You ever see Willie walk
You talk about the chocolate factory. Yeah
You seen that one. Yeah. Yeah, I heard about it. I've seen a little bit of it, but I don't I it's been a long time
Yeah, you know, I played Willie walk in that movie
It really is hold on one second. I'm going to show you because I know people won't believe me, but okay
So I actually have this little footage from backseat, and so you can also see Sarah's kiddies here
Let's see. So Sarah's kiddies and they come up right in a second. Okay, so videos. Oh posts, okay, and
There's a video of Sarah and me and all this kind of stuff. Okay, so let's see. Oh here it is, okay
Okay, yeah, okay. Are you ready mason? Yeah, okay one second
Psych yeah
You look like you're a skateboarder man or something like that the way you look I am I
Do tricks on skateboards I do all these here. Here we go ready here you go watch this
Yeah
Count to three
Come with me and you'll be in our world
You see that I supposed to be you site it is me
There's be a she plays by the board garden movie and then does that the same one I talked to
Is that the same one I talked to that's Sarah right there. Yeah, and that's that Trisha Licious
Um, yeah
She'll code her name is there too. Oh my gosh. Well, there she is. Okay, so you can hear her now
Let me get the volume on
Because she's been talking about me now
She still do live streams though
I want to change the world
So anyway, so I see he's playing like clips from my channel,
not even his, I can understand if it's like from his channel,
but he's like playing mine.
So I messaged him, I'm like,
why are you like playing clips from my channel?
Like what, you know, like, I'm like stop it.
And he goes, okay, done.
Then he restart and then he starts playing somewhere.
I'm like literally fighting with people like me versus NorCal,
this and that.
And then he titled it like,
Um be careful what you ask for or blah blah blah. I don't even know who you're talking about
Yeah, okay. Okay. Well got simple question. I have uh, I see j-dog up there the guy that freaking is like a huge fucking doctor
Um doc jayme rose docs me boston bridges
Um, sister, I mean, uh, dogs, you know, their sister, um, you know how they're like
Jada, yeah
Like saying like other things like be that killed her husband this and that I'm like people say shit like that about me
He goes do you want me to mod you like I'm like no, I don't want you to mod me
I want you to freaking understand like when people come in. I'm like on the panel defending myself
I'm not going at anybody else. I'm not going out freaking psyche. Like why is he doing this to me like he's antagonizing me
It really hurt me. I was like literally in tears
You know what it's called
They're doing for country
Okay, what do you think Mason?
Sorry, yeah
It's like can you still see me man? Even though it's kind of hard. I see you. You see me. What do you think?
What do you think? Are you able to still see me though like really? Yeah, I see you
I see you. I'm looking at it. Yeah. What do you think about betas? What do you think about beta? I
Like beta a lot. I think like
She's already mad at me and then I'm never I don't ever matter her
She's always getting mad at me and I never like say like me. I don't know
She's like kind of his bossy a little bit like and I what would you get?
Why would you get that way to you though mad at you? I don't know. It's like sometimes
It's always the people that the people that we like like or like are close to we you'd be fight with or something
I don't know. But yeah, I don't know what I don't know what Sarah's problem is
No, I thought you were a friend still so I think we are I think we are but it's like she's just mad at me today
So what about you and I those are we still cool? Yeah, are you gonna come visit me soon like you said?
Yeah
Okay, I mean waiting
You just gotta you don't have to wait too long though psych. It's gonna have to be
How long do you want to stay here for as long as you let me though?
What if I like saying you can never leave and you and we're gonna live happily ever after
I mean, I got a thing. I mean, I never had that happen before though site. So I gotta wait
Yeah, you can always wait and decide it. Yeah, but I kind of like I gotta see how it goes
It's like I gotta see how it goes first. I know I know
For me it will go I'm sure will be perfect, but I don't know if you'll like me
You'll have to test it out
unless you have the
Yeah, the full test of the
Equipment like what is that thing behind you though? What is that? Like I think behind you the thing
It's my logo, do you like it?
What are you gonna do with that picture in the back?
It's my logo, so it's like I use it for my logo
for my company, like for this stuff,
for like the channel and stuff,
it's one of, I have actually a couple logos,
but I like this one a lot.
You never had that though,
it's like the last time I was here,
you never had that though, like behind you.
It's new, it's new, see I also have
the eyes of a horse on my arm too.
How can we disappear in those like like in the camera though? Yeah, because it's like I need to fix the camera
Let's see visual effects and I can take it off
How's that look better? What is that? Is that your cat in the background site? Yeah
Right there. Let's see. It's tricks. Yeah, you actually have your cat back there. Yeah
There's eyes right there. That's what your tricks tricks. You want to say hi to Mason?
Hi
Say hi to Mason the cats. Yeah, I like cats. It's like, yeah
So like that's the only cat you got right now, no, I got four cats. Oops. Yeah for uh-huh
I have a Lola tricks Lenore and Rudy
It's like so are you gonna get back in the betas channel again like where we were before?
Yeah, I mean I was barely yesterday. I'm I go back there like sometimes, but it's like every time I go like kind of like
Her chat's a little mean to me and she's like a little mean to me
I've always like nobody ever greases me and it gets like higher. I like to go places where
and uh, yeah
She's friendly, but not the chat and then she like turns on me when the chat turns on me
So you want me to visit you sometimes so I can see what I'd like to be like see see how I like it to be like over there
Try it out. You don't like it
Get on the back on the Amtrak or I don't look at a car or plane. I have a roof
Yeah, yeah, I'm actually rooming my bed
We can see how it goes like first, right? So of course
I'm gonna go at your pace you get to the side, okay? You want me to try it out with you first so you can see what happens
Yeah, let's try it out. We will you okay?
Yeah, I'm down
Okay
You like to be on the top or the bottom I
Guess on top then right yeah, okay, I'll be I'll be the woman
That's good
No, oh
You got uncomfortable with the hell Mason Mason, why'd you go?
Mason where did it was just the conversation was just getting good, right?
That was Mason. I met him in Sarah Sarah's kiddies room one night. He's really nice guy. He's a little
He's a nice guy. Where do you go though?
He said he was straight last time, but I think he's kind of like opening his mind a little bit
But I don't know I think I might need to give hi summer
How do I look summer? Do I look pretty good today?
Let's play the summer song because summer's in the chat. Let's see. I do have a summer song
You guys want to hear the summer song?
Have it?
Summer
I might need to put this one off here
Okay, let's see if I got the summer song
Okay, and I do have these numbers on where is it?
I must have to get it somewhere else, okay?
Beasts stand by
Psychi will be right back
Okay, let's do it.
I'm in the summer slam.
Ready guys? Here we go.
Darn you Mesa
Sweet summer, Dickerson, everybody's friend
Sweet summer, wild and free
Mother of ten, with a heart that can see
Bird seven stars, let her love shine through
She'll laugh, she'll yell, she'll always hold you true
streets where shadows fall. Helping lost souls who thought they'd lost it all.
Prostitutes, addicts, she takes their hand. Bills a little mercy right where
they stand.
She's known
Ten thousand trials, ten thousand scars
She carries them softly, like the nine-hold stars
again. Sweet summer, fierce and bright, Kentucky woman with a lion's fight. She'll yell at me,
but she'll make me smile. Sweet summer, wolves with grace every night.
I'm just kidding. I hope you were just kidding too. I know that song was great. You love the song
Sweet summer
How are you my doing my babe, I'm talking to the men. Oh my gosh
Oh gosh, so I'm in a good day though. I mean
Yeah, these are okay
Surviving the show is still here so monetize
Still, still, what's it called, still, B.I.G., or, what was it, rap song, it was, ooh, gosh, baby, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little
But now it's not for everybody, you know, but I'm putting it down to an album, too
and
So that's on the way. Okay, so what else am I gonna do?
I'm gonna hear that one more song. I'll play one more
Spurs and flames
Please hide and seek with the shadows
turns every
She's the
I don't know really have it.
I could do it in the dance steps.
Do you like it?
The song?
I love it.
I could do it in a modeling form, but yeah.
I gotta do this song.
But I love it.
Oh, you made it for me?
Well, I will.
I'll make you a song that one's actually about like I have my astrology is like I have Lilith Scorpio
And so it's like kind of like interesting. Oh, yeah, I don't have Lulia than Scorpio
I was like what okay to confuse me a little bit there
Astrology and so like Lilith is like gonna be in one of the science like the dark moon
It's like where the thick they have this hidden moon that she's on the chart
And so mine is in Scorpio and it's kind of like your dark side or everybody's dark side
But if you like overcome it or if you like
Deal with it. They know they're like turns into like a superpower kind of thing
Did you see I played earlier today?
You're you know some of your appearance on my show and you're saying like some weird things to me like you're saying
I'm a bad person and stuff, but you don't believe that anymore. Do you?
Absolutely not. I mean what you were doing to me was not nice
Did you did you play the the things when you were saying stuff about me?
Now, because it was on TripKick, I don't have some of those clips of where I was talking
to you, but I don't remember exactly what I said, I know I pissed you off one day, but...
Cause I said that, I mean, I had good times,
saw you like naked or something,
and it was like, you're like, that's not your story.
No, you were talking about my teeth.
You were talking that I was ugly.
Oh, I never said that.
You said some really nasty things.
I never said that.
And you should really watch what you say.
So, I never said that.
Are you, remember when you have,
sometimes you think things that aren't true,
like remember you were saying like,
You know like people are doing bad I'm telling you I know this is true because I have it on the fucking of facts
Okay, buddy, but what did I say? I said why would I say that like that?
It doesn't matter it doesn't matter you were trying to defend beta in a situation that wasn't necessary
Okay, well all is I mean it's like I've seen I've seen you say bad things about Vita like kind of like off
I had to I had to she's been calling me bad names for two years
She's bad at meeting. She's about a meeting out. She was she called
She's been calling me her dad's maid that if she thinks that I fucked I
Don't think what you know when I said that I said that she thinks that I said I fuck your dad. I
Had to she's been saying it too long
I felt like I had to, I had no other choice.
Okay, oh I'm sorry, Chris, I didn't mean to like,
I don't think I ever insulted your looks,
I think you're a beautiful woman and it's like,
I don't think there's anything wrong with it
and you kind of, you know,
and I'm like, cosmetically, you're bad.
What was that about?
I mean, it's like,
jeez Louise, I was trying to be nice.
I mean, what the hell?
What the hell guys?
I do have a Crystal Marie song somewhere. I mean, it's like
I'm just I accidentally hit a button
I'm trying to I have this like a little tiny phone thingy
That's cool.
But I really am sorry.
You know, Psyche, I really, that made me feel terrible.
Like just accidentally hanging up on you like that.
It's okay.
No worries.
I appreciate you coming back.
You know, and I was just trying to apologize.
I don't remember like saying bad things,
but maybe I have been like drunk sometimes
and talking about people I shouldn't be talking about.
And, you know, I don't think there's anything,
I think you're a beautiful person and like, you know,
Sometimes I think that you say I don't think honestly honestly is psyche
Huh don't think too much about it. Don't want you to think too much about it. I don't I don't want you to make
I'm not making a big deal about it, but I have you here. I just wanted to say I'm sorry if I
Yeah, of course, okay, and I want to say you know what dude, you know, you're the the best
You are so you're a great person
You have a great
You're charismatic person. I think that you have a great heart behind what people think
It is the persona like your character or whatnot or they want to
They just wanted to see you as a gay guy. We just so fucked up
You know, it's so weird to me because like when I met you, you know what?
Like it's so weird to me. It was like everybody was like, oh my god
He's like the gay guy, right? And I was like, I didn't know if you were gay or not
Yeah, I mean sometimes I only I hardly know because it's like I don't think about my sexuality
It's like 24-7 like I just like you know most of the time. I'm not
interested in anybody then occasionally like I find I find a man I like
You know what? That's what they were making you is like. Oh, you're the gay guy when that's not who you are your person
You're the cat man. You're you know, you're you're a human
You know what? I mean you're about your your cats and your family and stuff your family
Look at them and say oh, that's a nice man, but I'm like you the gay guy, right?
It's always like oh the gay guy and like they put that in front like oh my god
They might like you like him as a person you're gay and like you know people get attacked really
guys get attacked for donating because they're like oh you're gay you just want to suck dick
oh you're like the gay guy right but the but that's but did you see what uh
these guys like can we like they do gay things gayer than me and they never
You know all like
Is there a way we can band together and ban people's channels off the internet?
Sure, I can make you a mod and then, you know, you can go at it.
Who's here that we, you kick out though, I don't see anybody yet that really bothered me.
No, Barry, we should fucking get rid of Barry off the internet.
Barry the turtle?
Yeah, I got I got somebody in Texas. I got a judge. I got a warrior in Texas. I can't get him off
I don't want to I don't want to get involved in lawsuit. No, I want to get him off the internet. Yeah, I want to get him off the internet
I
Don't know if they're like really kicking anybody off the internet for a man. It's like maybe I don't know if there's like
Even people in the prison have
There are some people that need off the internet forever like Barry
Well, thank you. Yeah, he did send me some dick a dick pic and a butt pic of himself
And so well, no, he is stealing from these ladies and then like do you know what he's doing?
But like a beta and like all these other people like he's like trying to make them like
He's trying to pimp them or something. Yeah, he pimps them
I have to watch out for pimps because like if I like hang out with them
Then I'll like then I'll wake up like on drugs and like some hotel room and I have like no much of old Japanese business
We gotta stay away from that guy and you have to stay away from pence
peps
Like Barry, you know like pimps all the pimps
He said peps or what?
I don't know. Oh, PDF you're saying daddy's. Oh, Kim daddy's. I'm dicking daddy's. Okay. Yeah. Um, I guess so, I mean, it's like, I don't know. He, yeah, he says, he called you his bottom bitch. What does that mean? I don't know who is. He said crystal's my bottom bit, my bottom bitch. With my pussy? I don't know. I don't know. That's, what does that term mean? Is it like, I don't know, but that's rape.
So he's raping
Great great great, sorry
So I'm gonna report you to the FBI
Barry well, you know his last name
I actually know everything about Barry. He doesn't know that my family works for the government
Okay, and the White House
The White House, are you Trump's secret daughter, what's her name, Mary?
Not daughter or anything like that.
Husbands?
No, the maid.
You're the maid?
Wow, the maid of the White House, what are you, do you, are you like, I'm in the bed with the tape recorder and you're getting...
It's private conversations when you sleep sleeping or with the Ivanka or whatever her name is me to the white house I
got
What do they call those little those old tags on every mother
Airpods, yeah, I just I just put them on little sprinkles. Did you put one on me?
Where do I go?
You have an eight?
Nothing.
Yeah.
I know.
I noticed there was a big air tag sticking out of that apple on my counter.
I hear.
Yeah.
Chris came to my door one day disguised as an old woman peddler saying, oh, sweetheart,
I'd like to share this apple with you.
And then, like, one half was way there.
It was a huge air tag.
Yeah.
I know.
I I know I had to had like my two friends had to pull it out of my out of my anus
And I was like, what is in there? It was this huge air tag and it had your name on it
Because it's a Christian Maria. Yeah, and then he had part hanging out of his anus and of the mouth
It was a whole mess
Crystal loved it. You loved it, right? And it said
air tag
It's a property of personal money. Yeah, it's a property of Chris or air tag
You're not supposed to put those on people like to spy on them that's actually legal
Well, you know, if you put your name on it, it's not
Unless I like stole it from you if you like put my name on it Alex
Alex and
Well, you have to put your name on it if you want it for me. Yeah, put your name on it. I was like, all right, Alex
Okay, Alex, I'll put my name on it. Okay. I'll take it soon real
Beyonce said put a ring on it. If you'd like it better put a ring on it, right?
I was like, yeah, yeah, she's like, all right, you're to get his hat this year.
What?
What did you say?
No, I'm just kidding.
I'm going to get what this year?
Well, I'm going to have to rewind that and listen.
Guys, you know what she said just now?
I'm going to get what this year?
I want to hear.
Because she speaks truth when she's trying to lie.
No, but Alex is very funny, but she doesn't I haven't heard anything Alex. No Alex does not know you
She knows me
She doesn't a video together
No, I'm saying like a year ago like when we were friends
Right, but she did because she was sending mr. Big poops over here to spy on me
Yeah, but poops, okay, you don't know that like the the the weirdness of Alex
I know a little bit. I mean, it's like I don't think she's I think that she's like, you know
Kind of like judge unfairly for some things like but we're the same birthday. So we're basically twins
No, you're not
We're not why not
We're the same birthday
You have the same birthday to your twins. Yeah, we're birthday twins two years apart
Okay
We're Capricorns like so but the same day. So we're very similar. We're very similar people
I get her I think
Well, what will happen? What's your prediction? Like do you think that she'll like get bored with me and like then turn on me or something?
What are you making a face for I don't I don't want to know I don't want to know I don't want to even
Think
Okay
I will tell you this Alex and I were really good I felt like we were really great friends
For a good five years
We weren't I guess she doesn't think that I was friendly to her because I would not
The the whole thing that she was you really wanted me to do some crazy stuff. Did she want you to have left her like lesbian?
Like what
What did you like illegal things again patron she wanted me to ride and like lie about being patriot
But I'm sure you wouldn't do that, you know vegan patriot and I did not I said no fucking way
That's what I told her. She's she offered you like a lot of like, you know
Do you know you didn't want to do it to Chris? It's a vegan patriot. You like her
No, uh, that's not what she offered
Okay, she wanted me to lie about her being a drug addict
Okay. I like to cover up for a fucking vegan. Vegan Patriot? But it is vegan Patriot. On drugs though? I've seen it on drugs. I don't know vegan. That's what I was telling, that's what I was telling Alex. I would, what, am I supposed to have a fucking fin for somebody I don't fucking know?
Yeah, she should have asked somebody if there's no vegan.
I can't fan for fucking vegan. I don't know that bitch like in for one thing
She's on drugs, and I'm not gonna think for her
Kind of drugs this y'all crack meth
Wait, that was always she takes like six hours to do it. I
Method I oh my gosh
Is it on or is it or as a dying earth? I've been learning about drugs
Okay, so Barry is never nice to any LGBT. He's pretending to be nice to me. Okay, and yeah, and by the way Alex Alexander's not a liar
she's awesome and
Thank you for the benefit of the doubt because what am I supposed to do about that?
No, I mean it's like it's like, you know, you're making a claim and it's like you're not really backing it up
We're like saying she tried to like you to lie about being a patriot. Like why would she do that? Like you don't even know
Sorry, I can't hurry in. Okay. Why would she ask you to lie about being a patriot? You don't even know a vegan patriot, I'm saying
Yeah, that's what I'm saying. She wanted me to and then she wanted me
She wanted it was like so weird. So it's obviously like just like some kind of fake
Right wouldn't you think that?
Well, I don't know. I mean I don't depend on her
Like she was like
Because she didn't she wanted to be friends with Trasha again and like all these people that she
Fend against me too. She wanted to be friends with
I think it's complicated when the other people start getting up. Yeah, she fended like that. Just Jen
She that just in is like fuck dogs and like cows and stuff online and now she wants my best friends
Yeah, she is an animal all online. It's she's the most animal fucked person on the internet
Where does this come from?
Jen
She goes named by Bobby Dylan
Okay, is she a troll or is she like a nice person I think there's a general she's a sick person and she's fucking nasty
So you what what she does to me is that she choice
She's like she's like so mad at me because I never fucked a dog or like
She's like so mad of a normal issues
Oh, yeah, a lot of people are judgmental. They have their own big seat
You're talking about crystal. Oh, no, no, no, sorry. You're talking about Trisha. You're saying Trisha. This is or
Justin um Justin, but yeah, trash is not as bad
Trash is as bad but trash is not as bad
Justin doesn't know shit. Justin is literally a crack head
She doesn't want to show people that she's a crackhead, but she's a legit bad crackhead and
She should not have like no, and she's doing like she's bad. I'm sorry
Like evil or like just like Michael Jackson bad. You're bad to mom. Oh, where'd you go? I
Don't know. I mean it's like she doesn't seem to be like that
That some things just like I know you wouldn't understand because you don't know the back story of her heroin addiction in her
She used to she fucked
47 black eyes at one time at one time at one time
One time at one time at that many. That's just Jen. That's just Jen
Most black guys at one time. That's just Jen
She's got that level. She won that
LD sister you're saying that's a little yes LD. Hey, guess who produced it?
You LD. Oh my god
Yeah, he watched his sister get fucked by a bunch of black
I'm like 47. I mean 47 is like so many. It's like
imagine like the line
Right, and it's like how many like listen the line was only black eyes. So yeah, there's probably like four white guys
Okay
Well, and did they get did they get the only four there was like the white guys get to go ahead of in line
There was only four there is like four
So is it so so there was 51 people or something 47 black guys and four white guys or no?
Yeah, okay make sense. I wouldn't be any women
No, just black guys just black guys and it was our transgender there
Just black eyes just black eyes
But for white guys were they the four white guys were they like the directors? I
Think they were
Okay, have you ever seen a cook a cuckold movie? Do you like those ones?
We heard of those a what they're called cuckold C. U. C. K. O. L. D. Oh
Yeah, yeah, it's like I love them
It's like for this like, you know
There's a married couple and then like some black guys will like come in the house and then like the husband will like
Watch like real close and sometimes they'll like lick up the C. U. M.
Never mind. That's pretty disgusting. I'm sorry. Um anyway, so you've watched that or I watch this
I mean never mind
This guy's embarrassing. I really don't I really I'm gonna be silly with the eye over just gonna gray
But I really don't know that stuff. You don't watch porn
No
Is it weird or is it you have time to watch porn?
Oh, I watch it all day all day. I'm watching it right now
I don't have a lot of time to watch
And if I did I would not want to watch for like with my animals around
But wait for the animals the animals are gonna see it and get excited or something. What's gonna have like what do you mean?
As long as Trishalicious isn't there the animals should be fine. No, my animals are like precious. They like put them
I don't think they care. I don't think they'll care if there's like that sir. That sir love
The other blankets they ever have sex the animals
What your animals have sex with each other
No, oh my gosh
Do you want me rip your fucking head off
But I want you to know do you want you
Absolutely, are you fucking retarded? I
Don't know
Sometimes I wonder um, but why are you mad like why are you mad now like what I do now?
And one second you say I'm great, and then you second second you want to rip my head off
It's just I can't I can't hear you my phone's breaking out like you hear me now crystal. Why do you want to rip my head off?
Hello, I don't think she can hear me
Crystal
Is she there guys I see her mouth moving but I don't hear words
Lou
Crystal I'm thinking here. Me guys shoot psyche
Jesus Christ, okay, her microphones working
My heart I can't hear me. I hear you. I hear you crystal you hear me. We're all good
Do you hear me? I
Can't do that
Hear me. Are you wearing where's your headphones?
You're just like hitting you in the camera with your head like this
Why'd you do that? Hey, have you met Mason? There's a really cute guy named Mason. He's looking for a girlfriend
I'm just like, you know, you're interested
He's gonna probably be moving with me. You can just like, you know, come hang out with them when he's bored with me
He's really cool. He's really cool. I think you know, I am
No
No online is we'll never is never okay, psyche
It's never okay to do what psyche online is never okay. What is that?
Like be yourself and like don't ever fucking like because like like like these people never know what you really
Like I look so much better than these like what the camera gives me
But
There's a lot these people give me a like is like bad
They always want to give me two left eyes, you know what I mean, you know, and that was my own joke
You know, it is what it is
But I like to look like two left. Oh, I said it. I said it about another person
So this person gave me two left eyes on a picture saying someone has two left feet or bad dancer
But what does two left eyes mean their bad reader or what?
or bad looker. What does it mean? Hello? I can't hear you. Your mouth
really is fucked. What? I'm trying to talk to you. Let's go. Oh my god. Sorry. My hand
was over my mouth. That was the whole problem. Okay. So, hey Gish. You know Gish. Gish is
saying hi to you in the chat. We have Nick Johnson. I love Gish. Sorry Gish.
Do you like all these people in chat?
Sorry, I'm listening to you.
I wanna listen to what you said.
I'm the only one that you don't like
out of everybody, because you said-
I love you, Saki.
Saki, I miss you.
Of course I love you.
Thank you, okay, good, okay.
Wow, I got you.
Saki, you're an amazing person, dude.
You know who you are.
Nobody needs to tell you how good you are because like all these people are pieces of shit, you know
Like like a lot of people are not fucking nice. All right, like it's so hard
I don't want to tell you that you're this and that because it doesn't matter dude
You have to do it alone, dude
Some like
Like let like just live my life with the isolated and not ever like no just like with this
Sometimes with the pain of like because everybody isolates you as far as like they bully you and isolate you and stuff
Yeah, and sometimes it's better to do that like just alone
Why do they do that to me though? Do you know? Oh, well, they do it to me too. I mean they do it to everybody that and
They feel threatened by
Yeah, that makes sense
because
We're so awesome, right?
Of course we're a threat. I
Think so exactly
Now they're afraid that you know honestly a psyche if you went out and you actually just was
You know you're really if you were more natural got a little natural or natural
Just took the camera with you everywhere. Just like a like Jim Nick Jim Nick is a natural. She's a she's a beauty, dude
She's like so good at this IRL she could really
If she really wanted to she could really do it. Well, like just
She's been doing a great job
She might need a little help just said like edit people like somebody to help her edit and shit
Yeah, she's great. I like I had fun on her show when I was on our show
We had a freak off with mr. Bigpipes and
Jimmy and I both belly dance to a mr. Bigpipes. No, but you don't even know
Oh
Oh my gosh Tom flash and I'm gonna mod a hide that person. I think first of all, I think it's a fake Tom flash second of all
Yeah, I'm watching the browsers. I'm not it's on dark dog fart network and
It's a gang bang with like 20 black guys and
You know a white lady in her house
Pretty good
Anyway, um
I'll wait for crystal to come back if she wants to come back one more time. I don't know but that Tom flash
Just a mod just like
Get rid of those people okay
So how are we doing let me see I
Love you guys about one more song we can
Tom flash always wins. Yeah, except when he doesn't like right now
In a palace made of whispers, Psyche lay in velvet night Her lover came with hidden wings A secret kept from sight Trust the darkness don't betray Love is more than eyes can see But doubt crept in like candle flame
Burning curiosity
Love is fragile
Love is fire
Born of longing
Bound by trial
Even gods can bend and break
But the heart learns what's at stake
Psychic child of mortal pain
You'll fall, but rise again
Alright, she held the lantern high
Her hands shook with desire
A drop of oil betrayed her vow
And woke the god of fire
The wings unfurled, his beauty blazed, but trust had torn them far apart.
And Psyche wandered through the world with grief carved deep into her heart.
Love is fragile, love is far.
Child of mortal pain
Love will fall but rise again
Through trials set by jealous hands
She gathered strength she never knew
Sorting seeds fed
I used to try to draw my phone out of the edge.
I love the sound.
I don't know if you can hear me.
I hear you, do you hear me? Crystal, do you hear me?
I hear you. Crystal, I do hear you.
Do you guys hear me? Hold on, do you hear me? Yeah, you made microphones work.
I like better guys like this. I don't know.
Make my window appear.
I look like a person.
Hi.
So what else is new are you like, you know, because I worry about you like sometimes because you're fighting with people and I'm like
Why is she fighting with everybody? Are you okay?
There's our spider on your shirt take it off. No, no, no
Mr. Mifty nickel don't say so
You hear me now
I hear you hear me. I hear you
Now they have a pretty good deal on some they're like 20 bucks I guess for like
Yeah $20
Got weed in my teeth. I don't think so. Oh, I did have something in my teeth, tobacco.
It's okay. Thank you, Nick. What's going on with Crystal? I mean...
She's like a drunk Jessica Alba? Yeah.
I scared Crystal with the horrible music. I did not scare her away.
Thank you
So you guys see my shirt today, here's my shirt
I said I'm fine. It looks kind of like a pistol
I like that a little bit. Oh, thank you. Crystal?
Alex?
Yo psyche yeah, how are you bro? Let me just say hi to you because I always come in here
Just like you know fucking with all the people and now
How are you my man?
I'm fine. You're good. Yeah, okay. You're looking good. You're doing good
Yeah, are you telling me the crystal or ease of transvestite bro? I
Adam's apple worse than yours
Well, don't you see the man? I just figured it out tonight
Christopher is a fucking man
Me to figure out that I'm beta you're gonna know you're you man beat is beta
It's the more he's a guy holy shit you seen this picture Alex look at the picture
The double the troll with the double face
You know the troll looks better than beta by the way beta scares me
Yo, crystal marisa man. No, sir. Yeah, she is
Legs are thick as fuck any transvestite can have big tits. She pulled up half her hair in front of us tonight
She literally did she pulled up a wig so she's all fake the teeth are fake
And then I started looking at the Rams apple that bitch has an Adams apple
Bigger than yours brother and nobody has an Adams apple like you my friend. I know you're a man
Look here at him's apple
That bitch is a man
This is like that's why she's all crazy
Oh, how many trains we got up here, bro. So we got yeah
Are you trans? Yeah, you see that? I'm zappel
Crystal Marie has the same thing going
That's a man
So we got a crystal Marie. We got flirty diamond. Yeah, we got
There's another one. There's like two others or three
Freaks, oh, yeah, you mean
You me I'm not exactly you be crystal Marie, Florida. I
Think I'm rich and demon is it there somehow
They're old they're just old trainees
But you like trainees now. I do not like trainees
You're not I don't know. I mean, I'm not gonna guess them if you want to have a dick in a pussy go ahead
But I don't personally I don't I like women, you know with tits and pussy like I
like women I
Just want to fuck pussy all night long man all night long make him come all night long a woman and a man
Damn your crystal Marie she broke my heart tonight, bro because I actually liked her I was like I'll marry that dumb crazy
Teemu teeth bitch
I think she had expensive than yours, but I don't know if you know what I'm saying.
Jesus.
Fuck.
I'm in the toilet.
There's an old man up here.
Look at this.
They're getting Cheetos.
A fiery Cheetos.
Yo, you know what I miss?
E-job Oblamoff.
You know what it says?
Do you just have sex with them?
Obamov is a funny motherfucker.
No.
He's gonna be his butthole buns.
Obamov, get up here, my man.
Ooh, it's spicy.
Whoo!
It's like I just...
I can blowjob to a bell pepper, you know, and have a nero.
I don't know.
I think that is.
What's the other thing that is I came up here and the fucking thing left
Now it's just you and me me and Dama
Crystal Crystal heard your voice and was like
Back now, but she's she's like was talking bad about people like everybody. I
Hate that I hate that I hate that
You come up here and start talking shit about people like hello. She's saying I'm gonna be alone forever or something like that. What?
So I have to fight everything alone because no like no one's on my side
I'm alone
And you listen to her or him
That's a guy. It's a girl. Oh, just look at the fuck. Well, the minus is what you think bro
Now what anyone says to you?
Sammonds earlier
My fine, but
They're so like oh really try to catch you and like something and it's like they're shocked at every every like those stupid thing
I oh my god
blowing
That's the best
So it's the best to blow things out of a force. Oh, oh my god
So contrary so YouTube's out of control YouTube. Anyone up here is insane
Yeah, you're doing the right thing dick. You're doing a good thing. You're trying to make your show grow and like, you know
You know turn it into a business and everyone's hating on you for that
Like oh my god, he's asking for money. He's a grifter. Like that's the point of YouTube
I want to help them make money too is the whole yeah, exactly and the funny thing is without you they would not be up here
understand
Without you and this platform this channel, they will not be up here crying. They will be
Jerking off like oh my god when it's like going live when it's like going live because they can't go live because they don't have a fucking channel
So they're waiting for you to go live
So they can come here and talk shit and you know feed their little whatever this shit is and then they hate on you for it
That is like psychological warfare from hell, bro
Right now terrible. Let me see if I so you want me to make a channel you want me to go live
24-7 so everyone can hang out and be cool and hang out and grow and
Then you know when I try to make a little what it is supposed to write ads like
Promise the ads don't pay very much. It's like, you know, I know exactly they think you're like a millionaire
No, this shit doesn't pay nothing until you have like a million subscribers
You're
Better than a lot of people in a similar a similar
You know thing, but I do have to say well look at this. What is this?
Well, it's such just such hateful energy
Like I don't get it that he's sucking your dick, right like yay psyche. Yay your panel when you're going live
You're gonna look then you start growing little try to make a little money because this isn't free and then like he's a grifter
He's a grifter. He's a piece of shit like he betrayed us like what the fuck
the
Anyway, I don't know the black guy brushing his teeth
That's funny
What it easy just talk what was that about like I heard like I'm say turn like saying oh
We shut down psyche's panel at 17 minutes flat. It was like
I have no idea what they're talking about. When was that? That's an old clip obviously, right?
I don't know I have I don't know what that was. I was in no clue bro. Stay turned saying we shut
Psyche's panel stay turns cool. You're gonna do that, bro. He wouldn't
By the way, I'm wearing a face thing. Who's that?
Crystal that's fucking that's my boy. Who do you think that it's that's Nick Johnson my peeps?
That's Nick
Is that a surgical mask
You'll take a goblin. Oh my god, you're getting way dick. You gotta skip back on the skateboard. I see fucking man boobs
Whatever in the tire dick
No, you're getting way too fucking dickhead. Yeah, you got man boobs. Look at him shake them shit
You got man boobs my man, this motherfucker
I mean, it's like a nice. All right. All right. No man boobs
Damn, he looks like Rambo
Peek-a-boo. It's halo motherfuckers. That's wild
The long chimney song yo Nick. Why don't you join ice ice?
Drop the age limit you can become ice tomorrow
They give you a badge and a gun and just go tackle people at Home Depot all day long, bro
But 200 grand
There's no more age limit every like police agency has an age limit like NYPD
You have to join before you're 35 years old if you're 36 or 40 you can't join NYPD
FBI the same thing like you have to join before a certain old fart date
And I just had the same shit, but now they took the age limit out you can be 99 and join ice
Man, you got a sandwich. Yeah, you can be whatever. There's no age limit. You understand?
As long as you're not a criminal you're a US citizen
You can join us tomorrow, bro. Psychi join ice
Actually saw a guy today FBI jacket and he was all tall and lanky and I thought to you I'm like that looks like psyche
Psychi will be fucking FBI
Yeah, so Crystal said she was gonna call the FBI on somebody I love her bro. If that's not a man
I love her if crystal Marie's not a man. I'll marry her
Page is out of question. She's in Canada. She she needs a Canadian lobster
Lobster oh beaters fucking nuts
Oh my god, I think beaters DJ Electro by the way
Yeah, yep, I have new theories
No, she's not it don't believe it don't believe it
Little bit crazy you got a little bit cuckoo. It was probably better eating all those sexual fluids
Anyway, Nick, what are you saying?
I said, Crystal needs her ass ate.
Ooh, Crystal's a black husband.
I think you're thinking of Summer.
Christie is like a slave.
I don't know.
I think she's one of my handlers, actually.
She's drunk Jessica Alba, Drew.
Here we go.
Chips show up as green screen.
She's not a man, you clown.
He was weird thirties. I mean, Canadians, she's knit, right? What is knit?
Oh, there she is.
Hi. Hi.
Okay, he left. I kicked him out.
Do you like Alex? Or no.
Alex, I'm Queen. Alex McQueen.
I like all Alex's. I've always liked all Alex's.
Okay, he left. He left, okay.
I think, like, I have a certain relationship with both Alexos, you know?
The two?
Both.
Oh, both Alexos, yeah.
Yeah.
I know.
It'd just be interesting.
I mean, I just want to...
I wouldn't want to...
Oh, I don't know.
They've met each other now and I don't know if they like each other that much.
Oh Alex, I fucking you know, I love my cop. Yeah, I'm a cop. You know, I love the bad cop
In copper cock
Cop we're gonna read him into right
Have you ever seen Alex?
Do you ever see Alex on the patrol? This is Alex's actual him in his uniform. Let's have a look at this exclusive video
I've been missing in my sleep
She's eating steaks, somewhere in the middle they both take a break
Keith Tray does not stick for a fishing pole
Chase her laughter like it's his patrol, old page
Don't you know you're the catch of the day
And this cop's got one hell of a line to say
Like we're gonna say I would never say anything, but like I was trying to make you say something bad
But Alex wouldn't page the phone low with them
You know what I hear is hi mama
Oh my gosh, you're so beautiful.
I'm so happy to see you.
I'm in Gens, right, you know what I mean?
Like, that's what I like to hear, you know?
It's like, you think I'm gonna waste my time
on certain people.
What are you talking about?
Oh, hi, mom, you're beautiful, what does that mean?
I'm saying that with these other motherfuckers,
like after saying I'm giving you like an example.
I'm like, you know, like, you know, I was like.
Uh-huh.
So did you like the song about Alex in the page or no?
Well, that's my message. I just got I'm just saying okay. I just read you a message
You want me to make a song about you crystal?
No, I don't want a song about me. I'm saying that you need to start respecting your homegirls
I am like who's my homegirls you and abida and page
An electric beat is not your home girl. She's nervous. She's like your op. She's been my op for two years
I told you that I told you that remember I told you that she's been using that weird shit like saying that
like that thing for like
like
I was her dad's fucking me.
Crystal, look at the screen.
You saw how to say it, dude.
You've been saying it for two years.
Crystal.
I said, well, you know I had to.
She's been saying it for two years.
Crystal.
She's been like, I had to, dude.
Crystal, do you see the screen?
Look at the screen.
Who's that shit? I can't see. Oh
Alexandra
I'm the queen. That's Tommy
on the screen
picture
Alex
Yeah
You see the picture
A beat and the troll
Yeah
Pretty good. Anyway, yeah, but she was really mean to me dude
I fucking had to deal with that and I was waiting to deal with her and then I'm gonna
I'm gonna wait to deal with her in about a week. Okay. I
Was before it's before Halloween
Actually, my Nana died on Halloween.
It's not my favorite holiday at all.
It's actually not at all.
Yeah, I didn't know that I'm sorry.
I apologize.
I didn't mean to come to that subject, but.
I kind of like Halloween, but yeah.
One of my last Halloween, it's like grandma.
I just don't want my grandma to expect, you know.
Yeah, my grandma died in Nana,
my Nana died in 91, but.
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
I mean my grandparents have the best like every parent my grandparents of all the parents are the best
I had the best of the best dude. I don't even I have
They had the best life. They had like as far as they they struggled of course
But they made themselves better
They made me the best person
I'm here. I'm strong. I'm a woman
Strongest fuck.
Can you say I am woman hear me roar?
Because that's so weird dude, but I will say that I
Would never do it without men
Because I had great men to support me. You think I wouldn't be able to do it out all my brothers
Well, yeah, I
Have my sissy my mother, you know what I mean? I'm saying as far as like at that part. I
Mean like me and my brothers. I have like pretty much twins. I have pretty much a twin twin
cool
Are you a lot of like or are you a full brother to sister or for a half brothers?
No died. They died. I'm sorry
They died when I was 19, when we were 19, it was, yeah.
They all did it, or 20, but yeah.
One of them did it, they all did.
Oh my gosh, what happened?
Well, me and my other brother are three years apart,
but we're more 20.
We looked just like, we're three years apart,
but we looked just the same and we kinda acted the same.
So we're more twins.
Yeah.
And you get along or you're still talking or what? Oh, we're the besties. I yeah
cool
Yeah, I
My family loves me. I'm like a glue of
everything if
Everybody has a knot
You know, I might not be like what you guys can I am the superstar because I am a glue
Uh-huh and without my glue you guys will not stick
okay
Without beta and without no, but you guys will not stick
But that beat I won't I won't let
No, I'm saying even without beta beta gone, right? She's gone
Where'd you go?
Well, she's in her Arabic world, you know, she's a she's in her, you know, she's in crack world
Okay
Airbit crack or whatever. What do they do heroin?
They just eat biscuits all day. No, they do heroin Arabic heroin
Arabic heroin that's what she's doing
Anyways in my opinion
And that's what you know
Yeah, so what else so what else is going on?
You had it like make it so weird and make it weirder um, oh my gosh
Fashion week or is this month? I need to link up for somebody. Oh my god. Listen to me. Listen to me
Don't listen to me, but listen to me. Okay
I have to deal with passion week this month.
Oh, hello.
Hey.
Hi.
Crystal.
Guess who it is.
That was my mic sound.
Do I sound like...
It's a little bit low.
Hold on.
Yes, I hear it.
I hear it.
Is it Crystal?
Better.
Do you know what it is, Crystal?
I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I
Man, you are getting better. I wish we could get better on like if you were like so
Do you watch my streams or what?
I try I really I like
Why don't you ever pop in, you used to pop in
Like pop in and chat and stuff
I can't, I can't say anything because you would take it to your fucking head and then you would
No I wouldn't, I'd say like hey
What's up, Crystal? Thanks for popping in.
Nope, nope. You could not take it nicely.
No, I'm not lying.
Well, just say that.
No, no. You can't take it nicely.
You can't take shit nicely,
so I know that I can't pop in and say,
No, I do it all the time.
No, but I will give you a thumbs up,
and I will, like, you know,
I do keep an eye on you,
and I respect you, buddy.
But, you know, I know how you are.
How am I?
Tell me like there's something I can improve on I want to know about it. Oh, come on
You're not anyway, okay, you're good
Like what did you say?
I'm saying it's bad. I think it's like you're bad
What I was saying it like you're bad, but you're not oh, no, I'm pretty chill
Don't I feel like there's someone doing there's something doing tell me about it like tell me if there's a specific thing
I'm doing that's like that
It's just the creepiness of it all
I don't know how I could outdo that like
I'm just trying to like get better at music
No, but you really are great. You're doing great
pipes
I'll give you a I
Want you to be encouraged? I want you to be encouraged because you really are a great artist
You have great boys. You know when you are being yourself and not like trying to show off
Or anything I think you have a better voice when you're just being yourself, you know sometimes
Yeah
You know
I get to cocky about well, I mean that's like if people are like like aggro on me and shit like I mean
Like don't talk shit to me. You're so fucked up shit. What the fuck's going on here. I
Mean, I'm just like you. Oh
What the fuck oh
Hold on, where's the check-in?
You fucking asshole, this person is talking so...
Oh my gosh!
What the fuck?
This person is talking so much shit to me.
I'm not talking shit to you.
Not you.
You sound kind of drunk though. You sound pretty trash.
So I do you know I have here. I have a tall can and natty daddy. Should I fucking crack it open?
I got a thing of ice cubes and a tall can and natty daddy
You should check out the beginning of my stream from tonight. I play this song
I got my like audio set up finally and like holy shit. It sounds fucking good. It sounds I'm playing um
The song from O Brother where at that's called uh
I am weary. I am weary. Let me rest
I am weary. Let me rest like holy shit. I literally I must cry when I'm playing it
I almost cry in the middle of it, but then watching it back, I literally broke down in tears because it sounded so fucking good.
Yeah, I do love that, uh, Cole Mountain, that movie, uh, Cole Mountain.
Oh, yeah, that's like Tom Cruise on it or something?
Well, that's where that movie came from, because it's actually a movie.
I haven't seen that.
I know that Jack White did a cover of Sitting on Top of the World for it.
It's a soundtrack for the movie.
It's actually a movie. We're it's a beautiful me. I it's one of my favorite
Like a big like
Wait, am I live right now
I don't know. I don't know what you're doing. I mean, maybe you probably are. I don't know what you're doing.
No, I'm not alive. That's, we get the same fucking thing.
I don't have anything. I'm not a live viewer yet. You're alive.
I'm live right now? What the fuck?
No.
I don't know.
Oh no, that's psyche. That's psyche.
But listen
Cold mountain is one of my favorite about our movies. Oh my gosh, I love that movie you too. Like it was like I
Love like Nicole came in. I love the whole I love Jack White in that movie
Jack Whites in the movie. Yeah
Like the guy from white strips. Yeah, Tom Cruise isn't it?
No, no
No, it's Nicole Kenman. Yeah, she got murdered by OJ Simpson, right?
No
You sure still alive
Hmm
That is Tom Kurza's ex-wife that is like
glory of
That's what can what she's an eyes-witch
She's Australian
What no you're not listening to me. You're cutting me off. He's stupid bang it. Oh
My gosh
I don't condone that language. No
Well, they're like some other they're fucking
Hatteria tanam or they're like some kind of weird fucking language
Aborigines
I don't know. I just want to kill him all.
I mean, now that you've said it.
Because the way you said it.
The guy named Abrams.
You were, I think, a racist Australian.
I'm not racist.
Yeah, I had a didgeridoo
You're a fucking racist bitch, and you're gonna get fucking showed off at your fucking stupid ass fucking
Pears house sit there fucking shut the fuck up, and you're fucking stupid ass fucking low life fucking
Oh, you're gonna get it by black dude. It's a Lewis
And you always like go into like threatening to murder me. It's weird
Um
She's still telling me that she had like a biker boyfriend that was gonna like hurt me and stuff
I met her
Oh, it was so weird and this like discord
It was all meth users in the discord. I didn't know that
It was called like
Natty ice or something, but Natty ice was like a
Code word for meth. I didn't realize I thought it was a bunch of drunks or something. That's where I met Crystal Murray for the first time
Who else was in there like Michael Stevens and Lena Moon? Oh
There's crazy people. Oh, oh dude, can you bring it back on here?
I wanted to ask about Lyric Moon because she told me that she died.
I heard that Lyric Moon died.